http://www.malindi.co.uk/privacy-policy-use-of-cookeis

ContactFind Us
HomeAccredited Training
Omni Healing TrainingLearn Usui Reiki Training WalesOmni Kriya Training Energy MassageDr Sameer KaleTraining at Malindi CentreAvailable Therapies
Integrative CounsellingBowen TherapyWEEKEND AND DAY COURSESRoom Hire
Privacy Policy & Use of Cookeis
We take your privacy very seriously and are committed to protecting your personal information. This policy sets out how we use the information that you provide us.We keep our privacy policy under regular review and we will place any updates on this web page. This privacy policy was last updated on 29th March 2018.Personal DataMalindi Centre will not collect any personally identifiable information about you (e.g. name, address, telephone number, e-mail address) unless you provide it to us voluntarily. If you do not want your personal information collected, please do not submit it.Non-personally Identifiable Information Collected AutomaticallyFor each visitor to Malindi Centre, our web server automatically recognises information such as your domain, the type of internet browser you are using, the type of computer operating system you are using, and the domain name of the Web site from which you linked to our site. This non-personally identifiable information is collected automatically, used for internal review and to target future improvements.Cookie PolicyCookies are small text files that are placed on your computer by websites that you visit. They are widely used in order to make websites work, or to improve the user experience, as well as to provide information to the owners of the site.Our cookies collect anonymous information on how people use the Site, and don't store sensitive information such as your name, address or credit/debit card details. If you visit the Site when your browser is set to accept cookies, we will interpret this as an indication that you consent to our use of cookies and other similar technologies as described in this policy. However, if you would prefer to restrict, block or delete cookies from the Site, or any other website, you can use your browser to do this.Access to your information and correctionYou have the right to request a copy of the information that we hold about you. If you would like a copy of some or all of your personal information, please contact us using:01559 372395We want to make sure that your personal information is accurate and up to date. You may ask us to correct or remove information you think is inaccurate at any time.How will we use the information about you?This website does have a contact form so we will use the information you have willingly given via phone or email to contact you back about any Courses or appointments. If you would like to remove all your personal information from our records, please email us. We will not keep hold of your email and any other data you chose to give us for any longer than neccesary.Cookies set by Third Party sitesTo support our website, we sometimes embed photos and video content from websites such as Facebook, Twitter, YouTube and Flickr. As a result, when you visit a page with content embedded from, for example, Facebook or Twitter you may be presented with cookies from these websites. Malindi Centre does not control the dissemination of these cookies. You should check the relevant third party website for more information about these.Please note: If you choose not to disable cookies in your web browser you are agreeing to us using them on our website.
Terms of UsePrivacy Policy & Use of CookeisBuy a Course or Treatment online
© 2000-2018 Malindi Centre. Site by Malindi WEB DESIGN.
